

# **NGUYEN VAN A**

### **MARKETING MANAGER**

Male

**May 19, 1992** 

♥ Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and nd demoralized by the charms of pleasure of the momen of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

### **EDUCATION**



### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. it over 2000 years old. Richard McCli administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. corporate administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

### **EXPERIENCE**



Sep 2007 - Present

#### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

# Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult ure other greater pleasures, or else he endures pains to avoid and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

### **Recognition and Gains:**

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to ar Indonesia Italiano Latviski Lietuviškai македонски Melayu Nors goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

# **ACTIVITIES**





### **CVPRO JSC**

#### Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer our page with draft copy about your client's business, they will read it. They wil' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

### **CERTIFICATIONS**



**TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO** 2004

# **HONORS & AWARDS**



**TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO** 2013 - 2014

# **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US think the placeholder t

### **REFERENCES**



### **NGUYEN VAN BINH**

director of cvpro jsc

**\** 01234567890 mbinhnv@topcv.com

### **SKILLS**



Words Photoshop Excel **English** Power Point • **Japanese** 

## **INTERESTS**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt sue pleasure rationally encounter consequences that are extremely painful. Nor again is there and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities